hostednumbers.com 2015-09-15

# Privacy Policy for HostedNumbers.com

## Our Commitment to You

PATLive is not a financial institution but we do need to collect some private information in order to extend credit to our clients and to service their accounts. We value the privacy of this information, we take all reasonable measures to keep it secure and we do not sell it to anyone. We are committed to protecting this information and to keeping it private.

## Our Privacy Principles

1) We minimize the amount of personal information we ask for.  
2) We secure personal information and restrict access to it.  
3) We do not and will not sell your personal information.  
4) Our privacy policy applies to clients, former clients, prospects and Web site visitors.  
5) We comply with all laws and proceedings regarding the privacy of information. 

## The Information We Collect

We collect the information needed to transact business with clients who select our services. The focus is on minimizing the information we need while making it easy to do business with us. All personal information is explicitly provided by clients when they set up their PATLive account. This includes the information we need to stay in contact with them (such as their email address), to collect payment from them (such as a credit card number) and to extend credit to them (such as a Social Security or federal tax number).

## The information We Report

PATLive has business relationships with organizations that promote PATLive services to its members. PATLive also has business relationships with other businesses who refer or sign up new PATLive clients for a fee. For business auditing purposes, PATLive provides a monthly audit report to these affiliates so that they can track the members and referrals who are active with PATLive. This audit report provides the client name and monthly invoice amount and may include other information about account activity as it relates to the member's organization. PATLive does not sell client information to third parties.   
  
We reserve the right to disclose information in special cases. An example of a special case is when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our web site, rights or property. Another example of a special case is when we have a reasonable request from government authorities at the federal, state or local level. 

## The PATLive Website

We host and manage our own Web site. It is kept in a secure physical location and we utilize state-of-the-art Internet security for a commercial environment, including 128-bit SSL protocol during the capture and display of sensitive information.   
  
When you visit one of our Web pages, some information about your visit is automatically stored in a log file. This information includes the Internet address of your computer, the time and date of your request, the type of browser you use and sometimes the address of the page from which you came (it does not include your name, e-mail address or other personal identifying information). We use this stored information to improve the Web site content and navigation, to help prevent and diagnose problems and to help us understand how to make it easier to do business with us.   
  
For the convenience of visitors, our Web site uses "cookies." Clients use cookies to memorize usernames, passwords and preferences on a computer so they don't have to be re-set every time. Cookies are also used to track Web page navigation. This information helps us understand how visitors use the site and how we can improve it. We do not use cookies to capture personal identifying information, such as names or email addresses.   
  
HostedNumbers.com uses Google Display Advertising data to improve the experience of our website for our users. These display features enable Google to collect data about our users via Google advertising cookies, anonymous identifiers and other data collected through Google’s standard analytics implementation. We respect your privacy and if you wish, you may opt-out of Google’s tracking features at any time. 

## Lines with Other Websites

Where we think it might be convenient for the visitor, our Web site might provide a link to another Web site. Additionally, other businesses, including affiliates and partners, might provide links from their Web site to PATLive's Web site. PATLive is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those Web sites. Visitors should refer to the privacy policies and practices of those Web sites prior to using them.

## How to Contact Us

This is the Web site of PATLive, a Florida corporation also known as ATG Technologies, Inc.   
For questions or concerns regarding our policy or this Web site, please contact our headquarters:   
  
PATLive  
Cedars Bldg B, Suite 200 2639 N. Monroe St.  
Tallahassee, FL 32303  
Main Office: (800) 775 - 7790
